# Mihail Deryugin

E-mail: snarksliveshere@gmail.com Website: <a href="http://snarksliveshere.xyz/contacts">http://snarksliveshere.xyz/contacts</a>

Address: Mitischi, Moscow region

# Computer Skills

Web developer with experience in PHP, HTML5,Git, Css/Css3, SCSS, Gulp, Compass, JavaScript, JQuery, Vue(a little), Laravel (more than Vue, less than MODX, unfortunately), Blade, PhpStorm, composer, npm, bootstrap3, bootstrap4. Experience in Content Management System such as MODX, Wordpress, Bitrix(include bitrix only for list). Strong on MODX, i create about 25 sites and several modules on this CMS.

## Objective

Motivated PHP Developer seeks employment as part of a dynamic software development team.

## Work experience

Ard media Feb 2017 — Present

PHP Developer

- Develop and maintain e-commerce and other responsive websites using xPDO, MODX, PHP, MySQL, JQuery/JavaScript.
- Created new websites for individuals and business using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Gulp and Photoshop.
- Updated and maintained exististing responsive websites to raise CTR.

freelance Jan 2010 — Oct 2016

HTML/CSS Developer

Created and maintained standart based websites using HTML/CSS, jquery, php, mysql, Joomla, Wordpress

Intercom dec 2008 — feb 2009

Technical support

Technical support in ISP company

## Qualifications

#### **Develop and maintain sites:**

- http://www.germes-gp.ru/ ( + developing compare module)
- http://alvita-a.ru
- http://6x9elit.ru
- http://allbesttoys.ru
- http://archivespro.ru
- http://stom-mds.ru
- http://elite-book.ru
- http://foreland.ardmedia.ru

http://twinside.ru

Mihail Dervugin

- http://nikolfleur.ru
- http://selena-beauty.ru
- http://tlgcom.ru
- http://pppe.ru
- http://tdpromhim.ru
- http://vip-divan.com
- http://sunshading.ru
- · ...and maintained many others

#### Github, developing, non-commercial

- http://snarksliveshere.xyz ( Laravel. guest account: test/test )
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/strela (Converted PSD to HTML/CSS/JS, don't integration yet)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/vue.spa (test Vue page)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/csscleaner (for clean unused css)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/laravel-upload.local (Laravel CRM, developing)

#### **ARD** media websites

- stroy.ardmedia.ru
- http://stom1.ardmedia.ru
- http://stom2.ardmedia.ru
- http://salon1.ardmedia.ru
- http://salon2.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo6.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo7.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo8.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo12.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo13.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo14.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo15.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo16.ardmedia.ru

## Education

MS in Psychology

**GAUGN** 

https://gaugn.ru/en-us/

State Academic University for the Humanities

September 2000 — Aug 2005

### Interests

Right now my interests are php & modern frameworns. At this moment, I'm starting to learn Symfony

# Languages

Russian fluent,

English mostly for reading technical documention, I'm a bit out of speaking practice

Mihail Deryugin 2

Mihail Deryugin 3